sc.edu 2019-05-13

# Privacy | University of South Carolina

This Privacy Statement governs the manner in which the University of South Carolina collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [sc.edu](http://www.sc.edu/) website (“Site”). This privacy statement applies to the Site and all products and services offered by University of South Carolina.

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. A User’s Web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their Web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

#### How we use collected information

University of South Carolina may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide services to the Carolina community and to serve other University needs 
  * To improve constituent service 
  * Information you provide helps us respond to your constituent service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * To personalize user experience 

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

  * To improve our Site 

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 

  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
  * To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 
  * To send periodic emails 

We may use the email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

#### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

#### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. Laws do exist in the State of South Carolina to ensure government is open and that the public has a right to access appropriate records and information possessed by a government agency. At the same time, however, there are exceptions to the public’s right to access certain records in order to protect against the unreasonable invasion of personal privacy of individuals. Such exceptions are authorized by both State and Federal law. Information collected from users of this Site, similarly to information collected during in-person visits to a government office, may be subject to inspection and copying by the public, unless an exemption exists in law. In the event there is a conflict between this Privacy Statement and a State or Federal law governing the disclosure of public records, the applicable law shall control. The Family Privacy Protection Act of 2002 prohibits persons or private entities from using personal information obtained from State agencies for commercial solicitation purposes. A person knowingly violating this prohibition is guilty of a misdemeanor and subject to the penalties specified in S.C. Code Ann. Section 30-2-50(D). 

#### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and constituent service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

#### Changes to this privacy statement

University of South Carolina has the discretion to update this privacy statement at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy statement periodically and become aware of modifications. 

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this statement and terms of service. If you do not agree to this, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this statement will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

Communications and Public Affairs  
University of South Carolina   
920 Sumter Street  
Columbia, SC 29208   
803-777-8161   

This document was last updated on September 3, 2013.
